<?xml version="1.0"?>
<listing month="October" year="2004">
<printheader><![CDATA[ 
Young Members invites outdoor enthusiasts to get involved w/ the AMC. To subscribe to our YM Events email list, or to view photos and trip listings online, go to the YM webpage and follow the directions to subscribe. Our webpage address is www.amcboston.org/comm/youngmembers.
<P/>
Questions? Want to learn how to get involved? Check out the Frequently Asked Questions page on the YM website at www.amcboston.comm/youngmembers/faq.html.  If you has still have questions or concerns, please contact the YM Chair (youngmembers@amcboston.org).
<P/>
To register for any of these trips, please contact L or CL before 9 PM or, preferably, by email.]]>
</printheader>
<mailheader><![CDATA[
Young Members invites outdoor enthusiasts to get involved w/ the AMC.
<P>
Questions? Want to learn how to get involved? Visit the Young Members website (<a href="http://amcboston.org/youngmembers">http://amcboston.org/youngmembers</a>) and check out the Frequently Asked Questions page. If you still have questions or concerns, please contact the YM Chair (<a href="mailto:youngmembers@amcboston.org">youngmembers@amcboston.org</a>).
<P>
For full descriptions of the trips listed below, including registration information, visit: <a href="http://amcboston.org/youngmembers/trip_list.shtml">http://amcboston.org/youngmembers/trip_list.shtml</a>
<P>
A text only trip listing, useful for printing or for those with slower Internet connections, can be found at: <a href="http://amcboston.org/youngmembers/trip_list_pf.shtml">http://amcboston.org/youngmembers/trip_list_pf.shtml</a>
<P>
The trips listed in this email are subject to change, so for the most up to date list of activities, please check the listings on the website.
<P>
<i>NOTE: To unsubscribe from this email or to change your email address, please follow the link at the bottom of this message. To change your email address, first unsubscribe using the link at the bottom of this message, and then re-subscribe using the link on the YM home page. If you experience any problems with the email or website, please DO NOT respond to this message. Instead, please contact Joe at <a href="mailto:ymwebsite@hotmail.com">ymwebsite@hotmail.com</a>. Thanks!</i>
]]>
</mailheader>
<webheader>
Below is a listing of AMC Young Members trips for approximately the next two months. To sign up for a trip, contact the leader or co-leader directly by email or telephone (before 9:00pm preferred). Keep in mind that with several hundred members, Young Members trips are very much in demand, and there are simply not enough leaders to organize them. Wait lists are maintained on almost all trips, and there is often quite a bit of attrition. For trips that charge a fee to cover costs, the policies for payment and cancellation are up to the discretion of the leaders. Generally speaking, if you must cancel, you will receive a full refund if your spot can be filled by another participant. 
</webheader>
</listing>